iceportal.com 2014-07-13

# Privacy Policy | ICE Portal

**OUR PRIVACY COMMITMENTS**

ICE Portal, Inc. respects the privacy of every person who uses the ICE portal. This Privacy Statement outlines the information ICE will collect and how we will use that information. This Statement will also tell you how you can verify the accuracy of your personal information submitted the ICE portal and how you can request that we delete or update your personal information.

We’ve developed our privacy policy from industry guidelines and standards, and local, national, and international laws and requirements. All privacy practices and methods described herein only apply insofar as permitted by the applicable standards, laws and requirements and as limited by the ICE service. In addition to the privacy commitments outlined below, ICE complies with your country’s privacy regulations. Thanks again for placing your trust in ICE – ICE Portal, Inc.

 **INFORMATION COLLECTED AND HOW WE USE IT**

 **WHAT WE COLLECT**

ICE’s primary goal in collecting personal information from you is to give you a useful, efficient and customized experience while using the ICE service, and to help you use the content contained within the ICE database more effectively. Personal information also allows us to provide services and features that most likely meet your needs, and to customize our service to make your Content integration smooth and efficient.

 **a)**   ** _Personal Information_**

When you use the ICE portal, we will only collect any personal information about you (name, address, telephone number, email address, etc.) if  you provide it to us voluntarily.

 **b)**   ** _Aggregate and Statistical Data_**

ICE may collect certain aggregate data called web log information (such as visitors, pages visited, etc.). For instance, when any content is viewed, our web server will log that information to allow you and the client to view the performance reports and statistics. We do not collect any personal information from any visitor who views any Content or uses the e-mail feature.

 **INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

ICE does not require visitors, who view content we distribute, to provide personal information. ICE collects personal information (including but not limited to your name, address, telephone number, and email address) from the Clients and Travel Distribution Partners using ICE so that we may better server their needs.

You are in control of the personal information you provide to ICE online. View all your personal data within the portal by selecting User Profile after having logged in.

 **Questionnaires, Surveys and Profile Data:** ** ** ICE may occasionally ask visitors to complete surveys and opinion polls about their interests, needs, and attitudes. Surveys help us provide better services and products that meet customer needs. Participation is completely voluntary and these surveys are optional.

 **Consumer Services and Contact Information** **:**  If you provide our consumer service representatives with feedback on your experiences with our products/services or otherwise submit questions to our consumer service representatives or webmasters, you will be asked to supply personal information for our record keeping and follow-up.

 **HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION**

 ** _a) Personal Information_**  
We may use your personal information to contact you. For example, we may send emails or other information with updated Content in the ICE database; we may respond to your comments or requests for information; or we may contact you if needed to help with technical issues or questions to help improve our service to you.

We also use personal information about you to improve our marketing and promotional efforts; to statistically analyze site usage; to improve our content and product offerings; and to customize ICE services, layout and Content. We may also use your information to deliver information to you that, in some cases, is targeted to your interests, such as destination visuals for areas you serve, new services and promotions. We believe these uses allow us to improve our service and better tailor it to meet your needs. ICE does not collect personal information automatically, but we may combine non personal information collected automatically (e.g., through cookies) with your previously submitted personal information.

ICE occasionally sends users who have opted-in emails describing new products, promotions or events. These services are optional and you may opt-out of these services completely, at any time. We will only store your personal information for a reasonable period of time.

 ** _b) Aggregate and Statistical Data_**  
ICE uses web log information (such as unique visitors, pages visited, etc.) to help us with reporting and statistics. However, web logs may be used if necessary to help identify any person attempting to break into or damage our website. We may share web log information with law enforcement agencies if we believe that we have evidence of a violation of computer security or related laws.

 **DATA SHARING AND TRANSFER**

 ** _a) How We May Share Information_**  
We will not share, trade or sell personal information of those using the ICE service or any visitors to distributed ICE Content.  However, aggregated and statistical data, as described above, may be shared with our clients, and partners. For example, we may let a client know that “20,000 people visited a digital brochure during a specified period of time.”

ICE also reserves the right to share the information to respond to duly authorized information requests of governmental authorities or where required by law.

 ** _b) Data Transfers  
_**All personal information provided to ICE will generally be stored in our ICE servers, which are located in the United States.

ICE adheres to U.S. / EU Safe Harbor principles. If you feel that Safe Harbor privacy principles may have been violated by ICE Portal, Inc., you may contact us, the U.S. or the Better Business Bureau Online with your complaint.

 **DATA SECURITY AND RESPONSIBILITY**

ICE is committed to keeping the data you provide us secure and will take reasonable precautions to protect your personal information from loss, misuse or alteration. Vendors, contractors, or partners of ICE who have access to your personal information in connection with providing services for ICE are required to keep the information confidential and are not permitted to use this information for any other purpose than to carry out the services they are performing for ICE Portal, Inc.

 **LINKS TO OTHER SITES**

The ICE database links to other websites. ICE is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content, not approved by ICE, of such websites.
